twistedthrottle.com 2018-06-03

# Privacy Policy | TwistedThrottle.com

**We appreciate the trust you place in Twisted Throttle, LLC, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it.**

We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please **contact us**.

#### Information We Collect

We request information from you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, birthday and, when necessary, credit card information) when you:

  * Place an order from our catalogs or on our website
  * Return an item or make an exchange
  * Request a catalog
  * Receive a gift package
  * Create an account at twistedthrottle.com
  * Subscribe to our Email Newsletter
  * Participate in a promotional event.

We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database.

We also gather information about how visitors navigate through our website by using clickstream data gathered with "cookies".

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our website. They also allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so that the information you receive is more relevant to you.

For example, we use cookies to:

  * Remember what items are in your Shopping Bag
  * Recognize you when you return to our website
  * Enable you to use Express Checkout, if you have created an account at Twisted Throttle, LLC
  * Study how our customers navigate through our website and which products they request in site searches to improve your search and navigation experience on the site.

If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please **contact us via telephone** to place your order.

We also may contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Twisted Throttle, LLC.

#### Using Information We Collect

At Twisted Throttle, LLC, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to:

  * Process and track your order
  * Provide the services you request
  * Contact you about the status of an order
  * Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
  * Send you the Twisted Throttle, LLC Email Newsletter, if requested
  * Identify your product and service preferences
  * Customize our communications to you
  * Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
  * Improve our merchandise selection and customer service.

#### Information We Share with Others

We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, shipping, and promotions management. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Twisted Throttle, LLC.

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

Other than in the specific circumstances listed above, we do not distribute customer information to other companies for any reason.

#### Your Choices

We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or other communications from Twisted Throttle, LLC, or prefer to receive them less frequently, please **contact us** or **[click here](http://email.twistedthrottle.com/public/webform/render_form/it82zj1a61b6eokzmhvkowug6gsk3/36eec9cd444e60912295a1027530ad55/addcontact)**. If you no longer wish to receive our Email Newsletter you also may unsubscribe using the link provided in the footer of each promotional email.

Please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can be sure to identify you correctly. Please allow for all of our systems to update with the notification of your unsubscribe. This may take several days or weeks. If, due to human error, you continue to receive our communications, please contact us again and we will make every effort to correct the situation a quickly as possible.

#### How We Use Email

When you provide us your email address, we may send you emails necessary to process your order or respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at twistedthrottle.com, you will receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information. 

We will not send you promotional or marketing emails unless you have explicitly opted in to receive such emails. 

To opt in to receive promotional emails, **[click here](http://email.twistedthrottle.com/public/webform/render_form/1wrj6i1sgjclgpqzljqtutwujasou/36eec9cd444e60912295a1027530ad55/addcontact)**.   
To make any changes to your current user preferences, please **[click here](http://email.twistedthrottle.com/public/webform/render_form/it82zj1a61b6eokzmhvkowug6gsk3/36eec9cd444e60912295a1027530ad55/addcontact)**.  
To be immediately removed from our email list, please **contact us directly** or navigate to the Unsubscribe link provided in the footer of each promotional email.

#### Links to Other Sites 

Occasionally we provide links on our website to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of Twisted Throttle, LLC and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review the policies at any site you visit. 

#### Updating or Reviewing Your Information 

To update your customer information (name, address, telephone number, birthday, email address and preferences), please **contact us directly** or **[click here](http://email.twistedthrottle.com/public/webform/render_form/it82zj1a61b6eokzmhvkowug6gsk3/36eec9cd444e60912295a1027530ad55/addcontact)**. A limited amount of purchase information also may be available to you. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information. 

#### Security 

It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of our customer data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities.

When you make a purchase, request a catalog or create an account on our website, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format. For additional information, see our Security Information page. 

#### Privacy of Children on Our Website 

Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

#### Policy Changes 

From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously contemplated in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will immediately post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically. 

#### Questions or Comments? 

For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you to **contact us directly** telephone or email. 

We hope to answer any questions to your satisfaction, but should you ever want to contact a third party regarding our privacy practices, you can email the Direct Marketing Association's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at privacypromise@the-dma.org. The DMA is the oldest and largest association for consumers and companies with interest in direct marketing.
